Finding Aid for Harlan Henthorne Hatcher Papers
Bentley Historical Library
- University of Michigan Presidency
  - Yearly Correspondence File
    - 1953-1954
      - Alumni Association (Box 6)
        (6-16)
      - American (Box 6)
      - American Council on Education (Box 6)
        (6-17)
      - American Council on Education (Box 6)
        (6-18)
      - Anonymous-Asylum (Box 6)
        (6-19)
      - Applications for Positions (Box 6)
        (6-20)
      - Association (Box 6)
      - Association of American Colleges (Box 6)
        (6-21)
      - Association of American Universities (Box 6)
      - Association of Graduate Schools (Box 6)
      - Ba-Bz (Box 6)
        (6-22)
      - Bacon, Deborah (Box 6)
        (6-23)
      - Baits, Vera (Box 6)
      - Bennett, Wells (Box 6)
      - Bonisteel, Roscoe (Box 6)
        (6-24)
      - Brandon, A.L. (Box 6)
      - Brown, G.G. (Box 6)
      - Ca-Cz (Box 7)
        (7-1)
      - Clements Library (Box 7)
        (7-2)
      - Communists ("Red Probe") (Box 7)
        (7-3)
      - Council of Ten (Box 7)
        (7-4)
      - Da-Dz (Box 7)
        (7-5)
      - Doan (Ira) (Box 7)
        (7-6)
      - Dorr (Harold) (Box 7)
      - Ea-Ez (Box 7)
        (7-7)
      - Fa-Fz (Box 7)
        (7-8)
      - Fellowships; Scholarships; Awards; Loans (Box 7)
        (7-9)
      - Fellowships; Scholarships; Awards; Loans (Box 7)
        (7-10)
      - Flint College (Box 7)
        (7-11)
      - Flint College (Box 7)
        (7-12)
      - Flint College (Box 7)
        (7-13)
      - Fontanna (S.G.) (Box 7)
        (7-14)
      - Football (Box 7)
      - Ford (Box 7)
        (7-15)
      - Foreign Students (Box 7)
        (7-16)
      - Fraternities (Box 7)
        (7-17)
      - Furstenburg (Box 7)
      - Ga-Gz (Box 7)
        (7-18)
      - Governing Boards. Association of Governing Boards (Box 7)
        (7-19)
      - Ha-Hz (Box 7)
        (7-20)
      - Hannah (John) (Box 7)
        (7-21)
      - Herbert (J. Joseph) (Box 7)
      - Hyde (Emory) (Box 7)
      - I (Box 7)
        (7-22)
      - International Center (Box 7)
        (7-23)
      - Ja-Jz (Box 7)
        (7-24)
      - Ka-Kz (Box 7)
        (7-25)
      - Kennedy (Charles S.) (Box 7)
        (7-26)
      - La-Lz (Box 8)
        (8-1)
      - Laing Report (Box 8)
        (8-2)
      - Lane Hall (Box 8)
      - Lawyers Club (Box 8)
      - Lewis (J.A.) (Box 8)
        (8-3)
      - Ma-Mz (Box 8)
        (8-4)
      - Michigan (Box 8)
        (8-5)
      - Moore (Earl V.) (Box 8)
      - Michigan Council of College Presidents (Box 8)
        (8-6)
      - Na-Nz (Box 8)
        (8-7)
      - National (Box 8)
        (8-8)
      - News Service (Box 8)
        (8-9)
      - North Central (Box 8)
      - N.R.O.T.C. (Box 8)
      - Oa-Oz (Box 8)
        (8-10)
      - Odegaard (C.E.) (Box 8)
        (8-11)
      - Olson (Willard C.) (Box 8)
      - Pa-Pz (Box 8)
        (8-12)
      - Pierpont (W.K.) (Box 8)
        (8-13)
      - Q (Box 8)
        (8-14)
      - Questionnaires (Box 8)
      - Ra-Rz (Box 8)
        (8-15)
      - Rea (Box 8)
        (8-16)
      - Reddig (Rhoda) (Box 8)
      - Regents (Box 8)
      - Relics (Box 8)
      - R.O.T.C. (Box 8)
        (8-17)
      - Rowe (Tom) (Box 8)
      - Russel Award (Box 8)
      - Sa-Sm (Box 8)
        (8-18)
      - Sn-Sz (Box 8)
        (8-19)
      - Sawyer (Ralph) (Box 8)
        (8-20)
      - Senate and Senate Advisory Committee (Box 8)
        (8-21)
      - Sink (Charles) (Box 8)
        (8-22)
      - Smith (Ira) (Box 8)
      - Stason (E. Blythe) (Box 8)
      - Stevens (Kenneth) (Box 8)
        (8-23)
      - Stevenson (R.A.) (Box 8)
      - Student Organizations (Box 8)
      - Ta-Tz (Box 8)
        (8-24)
      - Taylor (Clair) (Box 8)
        (8-25)
      - U (Box 8)
        (8-26)
      - United States Departments (Box 8)
      - Va-Vz (Box 8)
        (8-27)
      - Vaughan (Henry) (Box 8)
        (8-28)
      - Visitors (Box 8)
      - Wa-Wz (Box 9)
        (9-1)
      - Wagman (F.) (Box 9)
        (9-2)
      - Williams (G. Mennen) (Box 9)
        (9-3)
      - Walter (Box 9)
        (9-4)
      - Williams (R.W.) (Box 9)
      - Wills (Box 9)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 9)
        (9-5)
    - 1954-1955
      - Aa-Az (Box 9)
        (9-6)
      - Acknowledgments (Box 9)
        (9-7)
      - Adams (Paul) (Box 9)
        (9-8)
      - Alumni Council (Box 9)
      - A.F.R.O.T.C. (Box 9)
      - Alumni Association (Box 9)
        (9-9)
      - American (Box 9)
        (9-10)
      - American Council on Education (Box 9)
        (9-11)
      - Applications for Positions (Box 9)
        (9-12)
      - Anonymous-Asylum (Box 9)
        (9-13)
      - Association (Box 9)
      - Association of American Colleges (Box 9)
        (9-14)
      - Association of American Universities (Box 9)
      - Association of Graduate Schools (Box 9)
      - American Council on Education (Problems Committee) (Box 9)
        (9-15)
      - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 9)
      - Ba-Be (Box 9)
        (9-16)
      - Bf-Bz (Box 9)
        (9-17)
      - Bacon (Deborah) (Box 9)
        (9-18)
      - Baits (Vera) (Box 9)
      - Bennett (Wells) (Box 9)
      - Bonisteel (Roscoe) (Box 9)
      - Brandon (A.L.) (Box 9)
        (9-19)
      - Brown (G.G.) (Box 9)
      - Bureau of School Services (Box 9)
      - Ca-Cz (Box 9)
        (9-20)
      - Clements Library (Box 9)
        (9-21)
      - Connable (Alfred) (Box 9)
      - Council for Financial Aid to Education (Box 9)
        (9-22)
      - Council of Ten (Box 9)
      - Cross (R.W.) (Box 9)
      - Da-Dz (Box 9)
        (9-23)
      - Douglas (William O.) (Box 9)
        (9-24)
      - Doan (Ira) (Box 9)
      - Dustin (Fred) (Box 9)
      - Ea-Ez (Box 9)
        (9-25)
      - Economic Club of Detroit (Box 9)
        (9-26)
      - Eckert (Otto) (Box 9)
      - Extension Service (Box 9)
      - Fa-Fz (Box 10)
        (10-1)
      - Fellowships (Box 10)
        (10-2)
      - Fellowships (Box 10)
        (10-3)
      - Fontanna (S.G.) (Box 10)
        (10-4)
      - Football (Box 10)
      - Ford Motor Company (Box 10)
        (10-5)
      - Ford Foundation (Box 10)
      - Foreign Students (Box 10)
        (10-6)
      - Furstenberg (Albert) (Box 10)
      - Ga-Gz (Box 10)
        (10-7)
      - General Motors Scholarships (Box 10)
        (10-8)
      - Gorman (Box 10)
        (10-9)
      - Governing Boards. Association of Governing Boards (Box 10)
      - Ha-Hz (Box 10)
        (10-10)
      - Hannah (John) (Box 10)
        (10-11)
      - Henderson (Box 10)
      - Herbert (J. Joseph) (Box 10)
      - Ia-Iz (Box 10)
        (10-12)
      - Inglis House (Box 10)
        (10-13)
      - Institute of International Education (Box 10)
      - International Center (Box 10)
      - Intercollegiate Athletics. Board in Control of Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 10)
        (10-14)
      - Ja-Jz (Box 10)
        (10-15)
      - Ka-Kz (Box 10)
        (10-16)
      - La-Lz (Box 10)
        (10-17)
      - Lane Hall (Box 10)
        (10-18)
      - Lawyers Club (Box 10)
      - Lewis (Box 10)
      - Ma-Mc (Box 10)
        (10-19)
      - Mc-Mz (Box 10)
        (10-20)
      - Michigan Council of College Presidents (Box 10)
        (10-21)
      - Michigan (Box 10)
        (10-22)
      - Michigan State College (Box 10)
      - Moore (Earl V.) (Box 10)
      - Na-Nz (Box 11)
        (11-1)
      - National (Box 11)
        (11-2)
      - N.R.O.T.C. (Box 11)
        (11-3)
      - News Service (Box 11)
      - Niehuss (Marvin) (Box 11)
      - North Central Association (Box 11)
        (11-4)
      - Oa-Oz (Box 11)
        (11-5)
      - Odegaard (C.E.) (Box 11)
        (11-6)
      - Olson (Box 11)
        (11-7)
      - Oriental Scholarships (Box 11)
      - Pa-Pz (Box 11)
        (11-8)
      - Pierpont, (W.K.) (Box 11)
        (11-9)
      - Power (Eugene) (Box 11)
      - Q-R (Box 11)
        (11-10)
      - Rea (Box 11)
        (11-11)
      - Reddig (Box 11)
      - Regents (Box 11)
      - R.O.T.C. (Box 11)
        (11-12)
      - Rowe (Box 11)
      - Russel Award (Box 11)
      - Sa-Si (Box 11)
        (11-13)
      - Sj-Sz (Box 11)
        (11-14)
      - Sadao-Iguchi (Box 11)
        (11-15)
      - Salk (Jonas) (Box 11)
      - Sawyer (Box 11)
      - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (Box 11)
        (11-16)
      - Sink (Charles) (Box 11)
        (11-17)
      - Stason (E. Blythe) (Box 11)
      - Statistical Service (Box 11)
      - Stevens (Box 11)
        (11-18)
      - Stevenson (Box 11)
      - Student Publications. Board in Control of Student Publications (Box 11)
      - Summer Session (Box 11)
      - Student Organizations (Box 11)
        (11-19)
      - Ta-Tz (Box 11)
        (11-20)
      - Taylor (Box 11)
        (11-21)
      - Television (Box 11)
      - U (Box 11)
        (11-22)
      - United States Departments (Box 11)
      - Va-Vz (Box 11)
        (11-23)
      - Visitors (Box 11)
        (11-24)
      - Vroman (Box 11)
      - Wa-Wz (Box 11)
        (11-25)
      - Wagman (Box 11)
        (11-26)
      - Walter (Box 11)
      - Watkins (Box 11)
      - Wieck (Box 11)
      - William (G. Mennen) (Box 11)
        (11-27)
      - Williams (R.L.) (Box 11)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 11)
        (11-28)
    - 1955-1956
      - Aa-Az (Box 12)
        (12-1)
      - Accrediting (Box 12)
        (12-2)
      - Acknowledgments (Box 12)
        (12-3)
      - Adams (Box 12)
        (12-4)
      - A.F.R.O.T.C. (Box 12)
      - Alumni Association (Box 12)
        (12-5)
      - American (Box 12)
        (12-6)
      - American Council on Education (Box 12)
        (12-7)
      - American Council on Education (Box 12)
        (12-8)
      - Applications for Positions (Box 12)
        (12-9)
      - Asia-American Seminar (Box 12)
        (12-10)
      - Associations and Bureaus (Box 12)
        (12-11)
      - Association of American Universities (Box 12)
      - Association of American Graduate Schools (Box 12)
      - Association of American Colleges (Box 12)
      - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 12)
        (12-12)
      - Aviation (Box 12)
      - Ba-Be (Box 12)
        (12-13)
      - Bf-Bz (Box 12)
        (12-14)
      - Bacon (Box 12)
        (12-15)
      - Bennett (Box 12)
      - Bonisteel (Roscoe) (Box 12)
      - Brandon (Box 12)
        (12-16)
      - Branstrom (Box 12)
      - Brown (Box 12)
      - Ca-Cz (Box 12)
        (12-17)
      - Certification Code (Box 12)
        (12-18)
      - Children's Hospital (Dedication) (Box 12)
        (12-19)
      - Clements Library (Box 12)
        (12-20)
      - Connable (Alfred) (Box 12)
      - Council for Financial Aid (Box 12)
        (12-21)
      - Council of Ten (Box 12)
        (12-22)
      - Cross (Box 12)
      - Da-Dz (Box 13)
        (13-1)
      - "Dago Dazzlers" (Box 13)
        (13-2)
      - Departments. University Departments (Box 13)
      - Doan (Box 13)
      - Dorr (Box 13)
      - Ea-Ez (Box 13)
        (13-3)
      - Economic Club of Detroit (Box 13)
        (13-4)
      - Extension Service (Box 13)
      - Fa-Fz (Box 13)
        (13-5)
      - Fauri (Box 13)
        (13-6)
      - Fontanna, (S-.G.) (Box 13)
      - Football (Box 13)
      - Fellowships, Awards (Box 13)
        (13-7)
      - Fellowships, Gifts (Box 13)
        (13-8)
      - Ford Foundation (Box 13)
        (13-9)
      - Ford Motor Company (Box 13)
        (13-10)
      - Ford Company Fund (Box 13)
        (13-11)
      - Foreign Students (Box 13)
        (13-12)
      - Fund for Advancement of Education (Box 13)
        (13-13)
      - Furstenberg (Albert) (Box 13)
      - Ga-Gz (Box 13)
        (13-14)
      - General Motor Scholarships (Box 13)
        (13-15)
      - Governing Boards (Box 13)
      - Ha-Hz (Box 13)
        (13-16)
      - Hannah (John) (Box 13)
        (13-17)
      - Health Service (Box 13)
      - Henderson (Algo) (Box 13)
        (13-18)
      - Herbert (J. Joseph) (Box 13)
      - Ia-Iz (Box 13)
        (13-19)
      - Institute of International Education (Box 13)
        (13-20)
      - Intercollegiate Athletics. Board in Control of Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 13)
      - International Center (Box 13)
      - Ja-Jz (Box 13)
        (13-21)
      - Jones (Dr.) (Box 13)
        (13-22)
      - Ka-Kz (Box 13)
        (13-23)
      - Kennedy (Charles S.) (Box 13)
        (13-24)
      - Kresge Foundation (Box 13)
      - La-Lz (Box 13)
        (13-25)
      - Lane Hall (Box 13)
        (13-26)
      - Lawyers Club (Box 13)
      - Lewis (J.A.) (Box 13)
      - Ma-Md (Box 14)
        (14-1)
      - Me-Mz (Box 14)
        (14-2)
      - Medical School Branches (Box 14)
        (14-3)
      - Michigan (Box 14)
        (14-4)
      - Michigan College Presidents (Box 14)
        (14-5)
      - Michigan Council of State College Presidents (Box 14)
      - Michigan Week (Box 14)
        (14-6)
      - Michigan Week (Box 14)
        (14-7)
      - Michigan Week (Box 14)
        (14-8)
      - Moore (Earl V.) (Box 14)
        (14-9)
      - Na-Nz (Box 14)
        (14-10)
      - National (Box 14)
        (14-11)
      - N.R.O.T.C. (Box 14)
        (14-12)
      - News Service (Box 14)
      - North Central Association (Box 14)
      - Oa-Oz (Box 14)
        (14-13)
      - Odegaard (C.E.) (Box 14)
        (14-14)
      - Olson (Willard C.) (Box 14)
      - Pa-Pz (Box 14)
        (14-15)
      - Pierpont (W.K.) (Box 14)
        (14-16)
      - Power (Eugene) (Box 14)
      - Q-Re (Box 14)
        (14-17)
      - Rf-Rz (Box 14)
        (14-18)
      - Rabinovitch (Box 14)
        (14-19)
      - Regents (Box 14)
      - Relics (Box 14)
      - R.O.T.C. (Box 14)
        (14-20)
      - Rowe (Tom) (Box 14)
      - Russel Award (Box 14)
      - Sa-Sl (Box 14)
        (14-21)
      - Sm-Sz (Box 14)
        (14-22)
      - Sawyer (Ralph) (Box 14)
        (14-23)
      - Senate Advisory Committee (Box 14)
      - Social Security (Box 14)
      - Statistical Service (Box 14)
        (14-24)
      - Stason (E. Blythe) (Box 14)
      - Stevens (Kenneth) (Box 14)
        (14-25)
      - Student Organizations (Box 14)
      - Ta-Tz (Box 15)
        (15-1)
      - Taylor (Claire) (Box 15)
        (15-2)
      - Ua-Uz (Box 15)
        (15-3)
      - U-Nu (Box 15)
        (15-4)
      - United States Departments (Box 15)
      - Va-Vz (Box 15)
        (15-5)
      - Visitors (Box 15)
        (15-6)
      - Vroman (Box 15)
      - Wa-Wg (Box 15)
        (15-7)
      - Wh-Wz (Box 15)
        (15-8)
      - Wagman (F.) (Box 15)
        (15-9)
      - Williams (R.L.) (Box 15)
      - Williams (G. Mennen) (Box 15)
        (15-10)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 15)
        (15-11)
    - 1956-1957
      - Aa-Az (Box 15)
        (15-12)
      - Accrediting (Box 15)
        (15-13)
      - Acknowledgments (Box 15)
        (15-14)
      - Adams (Paul) (Box 15)
      - A.F.R.O.T. C. (Box 15)
      - Alumni Association (Box 15)
        (15-15)
      - American (Box 15)
        (15-16)
      - American Council on Education (Box 15)
        (15-17)
      - American Council on Education (Box 15)
        (15-18)
      - American Council on Education (Box 15)
        (15-19)
      - Ann Arbor Community Fund (Box 15)
        (15-20)
      - Anonymous-Asylum (Box 15)
        (15-21)
      - Applications for Positions (Box 15)
      - Association of American Colleges (Box 15)
        (15-22)
      - Association of American Universities (Box 15)
      - Association of American Graduate Schools (Box 15)
      - Associations, Bureaus (Box 15)
        (15-23)
      - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 15)
      - Ba-Bn (Box 15)
        (15-24)
      - Bo-Bz (Box 15)
        (15-25)
      - Bacon (Deborah) (Box 15)
        (15-26)
      - Bennett (Wells) (Box 15)
      - Bonisteel (Roscoe) (Box 15)
      - Brown (G.G.) (Box 15)
      - Ca-Cz (Box 16)
        (16-1)
      - Carnegie Corporation (Box 16)
        (16-2)
      - Connable (Alfred) (Box 16)
      - Clements Library (Box 16)
      - Council of Ten (Box 16)
        (16-3)
      - Cross (R.W.) (Box 16)
      - Da-Dz (Box 16)
        (16-4)
      - "Dago Dazzlers" (Box 16)
        (16-5)
      - Deans (Box 16)
      - Dearborn Center (Box 16)
        (16-6)
      - Dearborn Center (Box 16)
        (16-7)
      - Dearborn Center (Box 16)
        (16-8)
      - Doan (Leland) (Box 16)
        (16-9)
      - Dorr (Harold) (Box 16)
      - Ea-Ez (Box 16)
        (16-10)
      - Eisenhower (Dwight D.) (Box 16)
        (16-11)
      - Eckert (Otto) (Box 16)
      - Economics Club (Box 16)
      - Extension Service (Box 16)
      - Fa-Fz (Box 16)
        (16-12)
      - Fellowships, Scholarships,etc. (A-G) (Box 16)
        (16-13)
      - Fellowships, Scholarships, etc. (H-Z) (Box 16)
        (16-14)
      - Fellowships, Scholarships,etc. (Box 16)
        (16-15)
      - Fauri (Fedele) (Box 16)
        (16-16)
      - Football (Box 16)
      - Ford Foundation (Box 16)
        (16-17)
      - Ford Motor Company (Box 16)
      - Foreign Consuls' Lunch (Box 16)
        (16-18)
      - Foreign Students (Box 16)
      - Fund for Advancement of Education (Box 16)
        (16-19)
      - Furstenberg (Albert) (Box 16)
      - Ga-Gz (Box 16)
        (16-20)
      - General Motors Corporation (Box 16)
        (16-21)
      - Governing Boards (Box 16)
      - Ha-Rm (Box 16)
        (16-22)
      - Hn-Hz (Box 16)
        (16-23)
      - Hannah (John) (Box 16)
        (16-24)
      - Ia-Iz (Box 16)
        (16-25)
      - Intercollegiate Athletics. Board in Control of Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 16)
        (16-26)
      - International Center (Box 16)
        (16-27)
      - Institute of International Education (Box 16)
      - Ja-Jz (Box 17)
        (17-1)
      - Jenkins Memorial Scholarship (Box 17)
        (17-2)
      - Ka-Kz (Box 17)
        (17-3)
      - Kellogg Foundation (Box 17)
        (17-4)
      - La-Lh (Box 17)
        (17-5)
      - Li-Lz (Box 17)
        (17-6)
      - Lane Hall (Box 17)
        (17-7)
      - Lewis (J.A.) (Box 17)
      - Legislature (Box 17)
        (17-8)
      - Likert (Rensis) (Box 17)
        (17-9)
      - Ma-Mc (Box 17)
        (17-10)
      - Md-Mz (Box 17)
        (17-11)
      - Michigan (Box 17)
        (17-12)
      - Michigan Council of State College Presidents (Box 17)
        (17-13)
      - Michigan College Presidents Association (Box 17)
      - Michigan Historical Commission (Box 17)
        (17-14)
      - Michigan Week (Box 17)
        (17-15)
      - Na-Nz (Box 17)
        (17-16)
      - National (Box 17)
        (17-17)
      - N.R.O.T.C. (Box 17)
      - Nelson (Box 17)
        (17-18)
      - Niehuss (Marvin) (Box 17)
      - North Central Association (Box 17)
      - Oa-Oz (Box 17)
        (17-19)
      - Odegaard (C.E.) (Box 17)
        (17-20)
      - Olson (Willard C.) (Box 17)
      - Pa-Pz (Box 17)
        (17-21)
      - Pierpont, (W.K.) (Box 17)
        (17-22)
      - Power (Eugene) (Box 17)
      - Q (Box 17)
        (17-23)
      - Ra-Rz (Box 17)
      - Radio (Box 17)
        (17-24)
      - Reddig (Rhoda) (Box 17)
      - Regents (Box 17)
      - Reichert (Box 17)
        (17-25)
      - Relics (Box 17)
      - R.O.T.C. (Box 17)
      - "Role of the State University" (Box 17)
        (17-26)
      - Rowe (Tom) (Box 17)
      - Ruthven (Alexander G.) (Box 17)
      - Sa-Sj (Box 18)
        (18-1)
      - Sk-Sz (Box 18)
        (18-2)
      - Sawyer (Ralph) (Box 18)
        (18-3)
      - Senate Advisory Committee (Box 18)
      - Sink (Charles) (Box 18)
      - Solomos (Box 18)
        (18-4)
      - Stason (E. Blythe) (Box 18)
      - Statistical Service (Box 18)
        (18-5)
      - Stevenson (R.A.) (Box 18)
      - Stirton (W.E.) (Box 18)
        (18-6)
      - Student Organizations (Box 18)
      - Ta-Tz (Box 18)
        (18-7)
      - Taylor (G.L.) (Box 18)
        (18-8)
      - Ua-Uz (Box 18)
        (18-9)
      - United States Departments (Box 18)
        (18-10)
      - University Hospital (Box 18)
      - University Library (Box 18)
        (18-11)
      - University Committee on Policy (Box 18)
      - University Press (Box 18)
      - Va-Vz (Box 18)
        (18-12)
      - Vandenberg Plaque (Box 18)
        (18-13)
      - Vaughan (Henry F.) (Box 18)
        (18-14)
      - Vroman (Box 18)
      - Visitors (Box 18)
        (18-15)
      - Wa-Wz (Box 18)
        (18-16)
      - Walter (Erich) (Box 18)
        (18-17)
      - Watkins (Herbert) (Box 18)
      - Williams (R.L.) (Box 18)
      - Windt (Box 18)
      - Williams (G. Mennen) (Box 18)
        (18-18)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 18)
        (18-19)
    - 1957-1958
      - Aa-Az (Box 18)
        (18-20)
      - Accrediting (Box 18)
        (18-21)
      - Acknowledgments (Box 18)
      - A.F.R.O.T.C. (Box 18)
      - Alumni Association (Box 18)
        (18-22)
      - American Council on Education (Box 18)
        (18-23)
      - Ann Arbor Community Chest (Box 18)
        (18-24)
      - Applications for Positions (Box 18)
      - Anonymous-Asylum (Box 18)
        (18-25)
      - Association of American Colleges (Box 18)
      - Association of American Universities (Box 18)
      - Association of American Graduate Schools (Box 18)
      - Associations (Box 18)
        (18-26)
      - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 18)
      - Attwood (Box 18)
      - Ba-Bn (Box 19)
        (19-1)
      - Bo-Bz (Box 19)
        (19-2)
      - Bacon (Deborah) (Box 19)
        (19-3)
      - Bartlett (H.) (Box 19)
      - Bonisteel (Roscoe) (Box 19)
      - Brablec (Carl) (Box 19)
      - Ca-Ck (Box 19)
        (19-4)
      - Cl-Cz (Box 19)
        (19-5)
      - Clements Library (Box 19)
        (19-6)
      - Council of Ten (Box 19)
      - Council of State Governments (Box 19)
        (19-7)
      - Christofferson (Box 19)
        (19-8)
      - Cross (Box 19)
      - Da-Dz (Box 19)
        (19-9)
      - "Dago Dazzlers" (Box 19)
        (19-10)
      - Doan (Leland) (Box 19)
      - Dorr (Harold) (Box 19)
      - Ea-Ez (Box 19)
        (19-11)
      - Economic Club of Detroit (Box 19)
        (19-12)
      - Education. Committee on Education (Box 19)
        (19-13)
      - Extension Service (Box 19)
      - Fa-Fk (Box 19)
        (19-14)
      - Fl-Fz (Box 19)
        (19-15)
      - Fellowships, Scholarships, etc. (Box 19)
        (19-16)
      - Fellowships, Scholarships, etc. (A-L) (Box 19)
        (19-17)
      - Fellowships, Scholarships, etc. (M-Z) (Box 19)
        (19-18)
      - Football (Box 19)
        (19-19)
      - Ford (Box 19)
      - Foreign Students (Box 19)
      - Furstenberg (Albert) (Box 19)
        (19-20)
      - Ga-Gn (Box 19)
        (19-21)
      - Go-Gz (Box 19)
        (19-22)
      - Governing Boards (Box 19)
        (19-23)
      - Ha-Hn (Box 20)
        (20-1)
      - Ho-Hz (Box 20)
        (20-2)
      - Hannah (John) (Box 20)
        (20-3)
      - Health Service (Box 20)
      - Ia-Iz (Box 20)
        (20-4)
      - Institute of International Education (Box 20)
        (20-5)
      - Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 20)
      - International Center (Box 20)
        (20-6)
      - Intercultural Relations (Box 20)
      - Invitations (Ann Arbor) (Box 20)
      - Ja-Jz (Box 20)
        (20-7)
      - Ka-Kz (Box 20)
        (20-8)
      - Kennedy (Charles S.) (Box 20)
        (20-9)
      - La-Lz (Box 20)
        (20-10)
      - Labor Relations (Box 20)
        (20-11)
      - Lane Hall (Box 20)
      - Laubach (Box 20)
      - Legislature (Box 20)
        (20-12)
      - Lewis (J.A.) (Box 20)
        (20-13)
      - Ludlow (Box 20)
      - Ma-Mc (Box 20)
        (20-14)
      - Md-Mz (Box 20)
        (20-15)
      - Mexican Symposium (Box 20)
        (20-16)
      - Michigan Week (Box 20)
        (20-17)
      - Michigan College Presidents (Box 20)
        (20-18)
      - Moore (Earl V.) (Box 20)
      - Murphy (Irene) (Box 20)
      - Na-Nz (Box 20)
        (20-19)
      - National (Box 20)
        (20-20)